是这样 一切...
Okay. Yeah. Everything..
一切都感觉十拿九稳 就等明天了
Everything seems nailed down for tomorrow.
您感觉如何
How you feeling?
为什么每个人 都在问我感觉如何
Why does everyone ask how I'm feeling?
我要卖 板上钉钉了 我好得不能再好了
I'm sell in'. My decision. I'm feeling great
还有 把专机给我取消了
And yes, yes. Axe that chopper.
兔崽子们有腿走路,  -好的 没有问题
-They can fucking walk. -Right. Absolutely
回办公室吗  -去泛美网科
-Office? -Uh, ATN
突击拜访吗
Surprise visit?
圣诞快乐啊 到点下班的家伙们
Happy Christmas, you clock-watching fucks.
但在当地并没有引起重视
But where they are, not to a significant degree.
虽说如此
Well, that may be true,
北约在文化层面上 有重大意义
but NATO has a cultural weight.
全是老家伙
So many olds.
辣妹去哪儿了
Where are the hotties?
这玩意儿需要点新鲜血液了
Yeah, I mean this needs the living shit kicked out of it.
一档叫做“走近棒球"的政治节目
A show about politics called Inside Baseball
什么  -这也太特么难理解了
What? -Yeah. How fuckin'confusing is that?
他们有这节目吗
They have that?
康纳问
Connor.
"你们出发了吗" 偷看的表情
'Have we left yet?" Eyeballs emoji
好运表情 还有直升机表情
Fingers crossed e moji and helicopter e moji
在路上了  -简直绝了
We're coming. -This is unbelievable.
我家皮尔斯赢定了
Our PGN is just gonna crush this
还不是你家的呢
Not quite yours yet.
回归老本行而已 阿泰 来点皮尔斯展望
Business retreat, Telly. PGN brainstorm.
周日周一的节目 垃圾
Sunday Monday programming. Dookie
周二周三的节目 垃圾
Tuesday, Wednesday programming. Dookie
周五周六的节目 垃圾到家了
Friday, Saturday programming. Massive stinky dog dookie
不得不说 如果打开思路 上升空间是很大的
I gotta say, the upside is huge if we just broaden out
不能再 只面对大学教授播送了
and stop over-indexing to college professors
对吧
Right?
抱歉 我根本没办法从这群
Sorry, I just can't seem to tear my eyes away
谈论北约的 光头男身上 移开目光
from the bald man talking about NATO
我即刻硬了... 我想小小主推一下
-I have a boner... -So, my floaty, kinda
全球化 兼具超本地化的
semi-pitch would be hardcore international news
硬核国际新闻
from global-global to hyper local
杰西 要是你的话会看吗
Jess, would you watch that?
会吧.. 如果在播的话 一定会
Uh, yeah... Uh, if it was on, totally
没准 聚焦一下非洲
like, may be a focus on Africa?
每天都播 就讲非洲发生了什么
Every day, just what is happening in Africa?
马格里布 撒哈拉以南的东部 撒哈拉以南的西部
The Maghreb. Sub-Saharan East, Sub-Saharan West.
我绝对会看的
I would watch that shit
你才不会看
You would not watch that shit
我会  -这听起来就像
-I would. -No, I mean, that... that sounds like
今日作业: 观看这档节目
Homework : The Show.
不 重点在于 它的国际影响力
No, the point is it's global reach
这个网络 能引导大家来观看
It's a network that teaches you how to watch it.
或者 把你这堆…  -或者什么
Or, shove all your... -Or?
把你这堆催眠的国际新闻
.foreign report melatonin news hour
扔到白天时段  -喂
-info dumps in the daytime... -Yeah
黄金时段统统轮播电影“发条橙“这种
Prime time, we go full Clockwork Orange, you know?
怎么了  -是这样
-Hey. -Yeah.
很遗憾 格雷琴·杨 因接触了案件 所以退出了
So, unfortunately, Gretchen Yung is conflicted out
真的吗 汤姆找上她了吗
Really? With Tom? He went with Gretchen?
行吧 那备选是谁
Okay, uh, who's in... Who's in second position?
克劳利
Crowley.
行 他也可以
Okay. Uh, yeah, fine.
我联系了他办公室 他也退出了
I contacted his office. He's also conflicted out.
科迈耶呢
Uh, and Kohl mayer, uh..
还有布洛克和卡姆登呢
and Bulloch and, uh, and Camden?
是的 都退出了 很奇怪
Yeah. Yeah. Conflicted out. It's weird
行 我知道了 稍后联系你
Okay, great. I'll call you back
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 2 集
我们跟五个人都联系了 是吗
Okay, so, have we tied up all five now?
是的  -他们都是罗伊先生
-Yep. -And they're all the ones
办公室给的名单上的人吗  -是的
-that Mr. Roy's office gave us? -Yep.
老天
Oh, God.
喂 兄弟
Hey, buddy.
嘿... 那个... 洛根来了
Hey, hey, hey, hey. So, uh, so Logan's in
什么 洛根来了?
Logan's in?
他在楼上吗 参加销售会议吗
What, upstairs? In the sales meeting?
不是 他在办公室那层 他在办公室那层
No, he's on the floor, Tom. -He's on the floor?
别急 详细地描述他在做什么
Wait, explain to me exactly what he's doing
四肢和五官的动向都说清楚
with his body and his face
我说不好
I don't know.
他就是在溜达 贼恐怖
He's just moseying. Terrifyingly mosey ing
他在室内戴着墨镜
He's wearing sunglasses inside
看着就像... 圣诞老人转行做打手了
It looks like if...if Santa Claus was a hitman.
行 知道了 撑住别慌 我来了
Okay. Okay, okay. Hold on. Hold steady. I'm coming in
塞吉奥 停车 停车
Okay, Sergio, halt the car. Halt the car.
把我下午的安排都推了
Okay, cancel the rest of my afternoon
喂  -喂 汤姆
-Hey. -Hey, Tom.
这么说 所有金牌律师 都因冲突 退出了?
So, all the top attorneys are conflicted out. Yeah?
爸教你的吧 真他大爷的妙啊
Dad teach you that? It's a fucking nice move.
他现在是不是 想娶了你啊
Wow, does he wanna marry you now?
我不清楚你在说什么
Um, I'm not sure I know what you mean
我说 你已经约见或是聘请了
Oh, yeah, okay. So, you've met with or retained
纽约所有能用的离婚律师
every usable divorce lawyer in New York
想搞死我 对吧
just to fuck with me. Hmm?
我不清楚啊 小西 可能是萨拉搞错了
I don't know, Shiv. I think may be Sara made a mistake.
我爸的算盘 我还不知道吗
You think I don't recognize my own dad's playbook?
操你大爷 汤姆  -小西
Fuck you, Tom! -Shiv,
我... 我的本意不是挑衅你
I... I did not intend for this to be aggressive
但 我见识过你家在这种事上的手段
but I've seen what your family can do in these situations
我就想 一切能友好解决
and I want it to be amicable
我相信 咱们能和平解决
I'm sure we can fi qure it out
好 行
Yeah, okay
你想当我爸的走狗 是吧
You wanna be my dad's little bitch boy?
那传句话吧 狗东西
Why don't you deliver him a message, bitch boy?
叫他滚出我的生活 有多远滚多远
Tell him to fuck off and stay out of my life
有没有发生什么 现在是什么情况
Okay, so what's happening? What's happening?
他还是一直走来走去
Okay, so he's stil I just kind a walking around
但隐隐约约有点想要刀人的样子
but with a slight sense that he might kill someone.
跟"大白鲨”里一样
It's like Jaws.
如果电影里的所有人都是给大白鲨打工的话
If... if everyone in Jaws worked for Jaws.
好的
Yeah.
他大声呵斥了一次  -继续说
-So, he did one big shout. -Right
他不喜欢
He does not like
选举倒计时的样式
the countdown-to-election chyron s
他不喜欢新字体 说是太小了
he hates the new font, it's too small
太谄媚了什么的 气压很低沉
It's too ingratiating. It's a really bad vibe.
这.. 到底什么情况 你觉得呢
What... what is this, do you think?
不知道 可能他只是想 在深夜秀播放你的
I don't know. Maybe he just wants to play your sex tape
性爱录像吧 格雷格
on Late Night, Greg
想什么呢 新的时代要开始了 格雷格
No, the future starts now, Greg
一旦董事会正式通过提案
You know, once... once the board rubber-stamps
有关监察部门也批准通过
and once the regulators nod the deal through
三四个月后 韦斯达就没了
three, four months, Way star is gone.
这就是我们的新家
This will be home.
所以 他会经常来吗
So, he's gonna be here all the time?
现身吗  -对 没错
In person? -Yeah. Yep. Yep.
像核战争的号角一样转悠
Hanging around like the threat of nuclear war.
我去了  -去吧
Here we go. -Go get him.
你好哇 老板先生
Hey, hey. Hey, sir, Mr. Boss Man.
只一封邮件
One email
真可谓斯达汉诺夫[劳动英雄]精神呢
Fucking St akha nov ites in here
请千万别累坏了
Please, don't exhaust yourself
您怎么看选举季的改装效果
What do you think of the, uh, election refit?
钱花得不少 这不跟飞机库似的吗
Oh, yeah, pretty fucking penny. It's an aircraft hangar
空调的电费是多少
What's the air-con bill?
希德很喜欢这种空间感
Well, yeah, Cyd really loves the sense of space
很有意思
It's certainly interesting
她人呢
Where is she?
希德吗 歌剧汇演季期间
Cyd? Oh, she doesn't tend to stay late
她一般不会待太晚 你来了 希德
when it's opera season. Oh. Hey, Cyd
老板 我刚刚在忙 没看见你
Oh, boss. I didn't see you. I was busy
不过 我看到我的社交秘书
But I can see that my social secretary's
正在招待您  -你们看那盘试镜了吗
been looking after you. -Have you watched the tape?
汤姆呢  -什么
-Tom? -Hmm?
凯莉的试镜带 你看了吗
Kerry's tape. Have you watched it?
你觉得如何
What do you think?
凯莉的吗
Of Kerry?
是说她的主持人试镜表现吗
What do I think of her audition to be an anchor?
对
Yes
这个.. 您怎么看 洛根
Well, did you... What... what do you think, Logan?
不不不 你先说
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. You go first
我... 还挺喜欢的
Well, I think... I think I liked it
她有两把刷子的  -确实
-I mean, she's got something. -Oh, she really does.
那我们....
Yeah, should we.
给她一档栏目怎么样
You thinking of giving her a slot?
因为我个人觉得
Because I... I personally think
这会很有意思
that... that could be a very interesting idea.
对吧  -我不参与
Right? -I'm keeping out.
她是我的助手
She's my assistant.
我来插手的话 显得太不专业了
It would be very unprofessional of me to get involved
你们俩位英明的领导做主就行
Whatever you two geniuses think.
现在我想给大家鼓鼓劲 讲一小段
Now, I want to talk to them, a little speech
在中间某个地方
Somewhere down here in the middle
能近距离跟大家接触
Man of the people.
晚上好 我是凯莉·卡斯特拉巴特
Good evening, I'm Kerry Castell abate,
以下是今晚的热点新闻  -目前还行
-and these are our top stories tonight. -Doing great so far
你看上去很蠢
You look stupid
密苏里州警...警方..密苏里州警方
Missouri State poli... police... Missouri State Police
发布了安珀警戒  -惨不忍睹
have issued an AMBER Alert... -Oh, my goodness.
官方认为 已有两名儿童被绑架
As two children are believed to have been abducted
他们最后一次 出现在大众视线 是在
They were last seen outside the school gates
学校大门 等待母亲接回
waiting for their mother to collect them
好突然的笑容
And then sudden smile
警方呼吁大家...
The police are appealing for anyone.
必须表现得自然点 不然机器人身份就露馅了
Must act natural to fool the humans.
一项医学研究表明…
And a new medical study has found that.
她真的播得一团糟
She's doing the shit out of this news
最多可以延长五年寿命而三杯…
Can extend your life up to five years while three cups..
爸曾经是神一样的存在  -将减短至两年 谁会想到呢
-Man, Dad was a god. -Can reduce it by two. Who knows?
也许是时候改为喝茶了
Maybe it's time to switch to tea
但是 明天他就要把公司卖给瑞典黑客
But tomorrow, he's selling the empire to a 4chan Swede
还给被潜的人安排工作
and dishing out jobs for blow ies.
小西  -你好哇
-Shiv? -Hey
桑蒂
Uh, Sandi, hi.
希望你不介意
Uh, I hope you don't mind.
我正准备给你发信息的
I was gonna try and send something
但是一想 干脆直接打给你算了 事情有点急
but I thought I'd just call'cause it's kind of urgent.
你方便吗  -这个
Hope that's okay. -Um, uh
方便 不介意 怎么了
yeah, no, of course. Um, what's up?
是康纳婚礼的事吗
Is it about Connor's wedding?
我真的很抱歉去不了
Because that was such a regretful no.
不不不 完全两码事
No. No, no, no. This is completely different.
是 关于我们上回聊的 以及你的报价
It's, uh, just about our chat and your pitch.
你知道的 我刚刚在想
You know, I was just, well, thinking
也许是我太草率了
may be I was a little hasty
这样啊  -对
Uh-huh! -Yeah.
你的哥哥们也这样觉得吗 还是依然拒绝
And do your siblings feel the same or still no?
不清楚 我还没找到合适的机会
Well, no, I haven't had a chance
跟他们谈这个 但是我打算时不时聊聊
to talk to them about it yet, but I'm gonna bounce it around
看看能不能说服他们 因为你懂的
see if I can't persuade them, because, you know,
我也觉得... 多赚点钱
I agree there's a... There's a lot of upside there
确实有很多好处
to get a little more money
这一点我当然同意
Well, I mean, obviously, I agree,
但是 董事会就在明天了 小西
but, uh, the board meeting is tomorrow, Shiv.
那你看 我能不能.
Uh, well, look, can I just.
我可以再联系你吗
Can I put you on alert,
万一还有讨论的余地
just in case there is room for a discussion there?
我只想说.. 这还是尚待争论的问题
And... and just to say that this is a live issue for me.
你知道的 也许
You know, may be..
也许我们不会直接默许 也许...
Maybe we don't just wave this through. May be.
可能这会激怒我爸
Maybe it pisses off my dad
但也有可能不会
but maybe that's okay
对吗  -对 当然
Yeah? -Yeah. Absolutely
我们回头再聊 可以吗 桑蒂
Maybe we can circle back. Is that okay, Sandi?
今日美国...
And the USA Today..
再放一次 再放一次  -太好看了 太好看了
Again, again, again. -It's so good. It's so good
太诡异了
Oh, what! Kinky!
再放一次  -再播一遍
One more. -Roll it through again
还要看吗  -最后一次
-Again -One more.
快按按钮啊
Go press the button.
晚上好 我是凯莉·卡斯特拉巴特
Good evening, I'm Kerry Castell abate.
如果他在电视播这个 就很容易被打包成
If he puts this on air, this is, like, easily packaged
完全丧失判断力和控制力的证据  -是的
as symptomatic of total loss of judgement and control. -Yeah.
各位 他们已经
Um, guys, they're actually.
是的 我知道..
Yeah, I know..
直升机已经在坪里等了
Transpo's on the tarmac.
等着带你们去康纳的婚礼彩排
It's waiting to take you to Connor's rehearsal
他在催我
He's texting me.
是吗 好吧,  -这可太... 太特别了
Oh, he is? Yep. -This is... this is special
我... 我觉得 要更稳固一点比较好
I... I'd prefer something a little more stable.
没事 我又不会长篇大论
Yeah. Uh, no, there's no need for a song and dance.
简单点 真诚点 就行
Let's keep it cheap and cheerful
汤姆  -在
-Tom? -Yeah?
你可以介绍我入场吗
Will you, uh, do a little intro for me?
调动一下气氛  -站…站在上面吗
Sprinkle a little sugar? -Up... up there?
是的  -当然
Yeah. -Of course.
在上面...当然  -好的
On the... Yeah, sure. -Yeah.
好了 好了
Okay. Okay.
各位 大家好
Hey, guys. Hey. Hi
就是来问候大家 请大家靠近点
Just want to say hi. Um, come on over.
过去几周很忙
Yeah, it's been a tough few weeks
伴随着即将到来的选举
Election coming into view, um..
很感谢大家 也感谢我的"犯罪同伙“希德
Yeah, I appreciate you all and Cyd, my partner in crime.
希望大家 继续
And, uh, from my POV,you know,
保持干劲 因为我们在蒸蒸日上
keep cranking 'cause we're doing great
业绩每周上升百分之三
Up three percent in the demo week over week
但是我们可以做得更好
But, you know, we can do more, uh
可以每年上升百分之十五
up 15 percent, uh,year over year.
还有
And, uh..
大家...做得很好 那么很荣幸地欢迎
Just... It's great work. And, uh, Just w... Real pleasure
大人物来给我们讲话
to have the big man here to give us some, uh
请上台来 先生
some support. So, sir. Up you come
来吧 需要帮助吗 不用吗 好的
Okay. Come on up. Want help? No? Okay
要贴面礼吗
I could give you a kiss from here
下午好 各位下午好
Good afternoon, everybody. Good afternoon.
每年同比上升百分之十五
Uh, 15 percent up year on year?
可惜的是 我们的支出上升了百分之四十
Well, it's a shame we're up 40 on costs,
但是我猜... 我猜最后都会扯平的
but I guess... I guess it even s itself out in the end
是这回事吗
I mean, does it?
十五等于四十吗 各位
Is 15 equal to 40, pal?
不等于 不等于 很好
-No. -No! Good!
看来脑子还算得清数
Good head for numbers!
好吧 你们都是好员工,
All right. You're good folks
你们都是翘楚 不然也不会站在这
You're the best or you wouldn't be in here.
但是 你们要为我认真点
But you've got to knuckle down for me
韦斯达我暂时不能多说
Way star, I can't say too much as yet.
但是 我会花更多的时间在这里
but I'm going to be spending a lot more time in here
和你们一起 因为我爱这个地方
with you lot, because I love it in here.
我他妈爱这个地方
I fucking love it!
所以...我不想知道
So... I don't wanna know
每周上升百分之三这些细节
about three percent week on week,
我只想知道 我们在秒杀竞争对手
I wanna know that we're killing the opposition!
我想割断他们的喉
I wanna be cutting their throats!
我们的对手 应该
Our rivals should be checking in
坐着他们的专车来参观
out the back of their chauffeured cars
因为 他们不敢相信 我们做了什么
because they can't believe what we did.
太激烈了 太真实了
So fucking spicy, so true.
一个 所有人都知道 但是没有人说的事实 因为..
Something everyone knows but nobody says because.
他们太他妈懦弱了 对吗
they're too fucking lily-livered. Huh?
他们 不敢相信我们说的话
They can not believe what we said,
也不敢信 我们真的说过了
and the fact that we fucking said it!
他们是高速公路上被碾压的边角余料
They're fucking jam smears on the highway!
现在
Now...
任何人 任何相信我会退出的人
anyone, anyone who believes that I'm getting out
请把彩旗塞进你的屁眼
please shove the bunting up your ass
这绝不是尽头
This is not the end.
我要创造更好的东西
I'm gonna build something better
发展更快 体量更轻 学识渊博 涉猎更广
Something faster, lighter, leaner, wilder
我要在这里跟你们一起开始
And I'm gonna do it from in here with you lot!
你们就是一群海盗
You're fucking pirates!
好吗 好吗 干就完了
All right? All right? Yeah!
GOJO项目结束之后
Who are you most excited about never having to see again
你们最不想见到谁  -雨果
-once GoJo closes? -Uh, Hugo.
弗兰克 卡尔
Frank Karl
你呢 那个
-What about you? -Hey, uh
等等 不对不对 什么
Wait，No.....no, -What？
我们坐不了  -什么
We can't get on. -What?
我不知道 出了点问题
don't know. Uh, there's a problem
抱歉 什么  -有新政策了
-Excuse me. What? -There's a new policy.
显然  -什么
-apparently. -What?
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what this is
但是 我无权让你们
but, apparently, I'm not authorized
起飞
to let you take off
谁有权力呢  -公司刚刚发的通知
Who is? -The company has just sent word.
什么 我们就是公司  -对啊
Uh, what? We are the company. -Yeah.
我们老爸是首席执行官  -好吧
Our dad is the CEO. -Okay
好吧 好吧  -对吗
Okay, okay. -Right?
是的  -怎么
-Yeah. -What?
怎么了  -什么
-What? -What?
是爸
It's Dad.
他在玩我们
He's fucking with us.
好吗 他知道
Right, he knows
我们在采取行动 好吧
we're out here making moves. -Okay
他被惹毛了
His feathers are ruffled
我们要登机了
So, we're just gonna get on
有什么事 后面再说吧
and we're gonna figure it out later, okay?
我...我很抱歉 我不能让你们登机
I'm... I'm... I'm really sorry, I'm not able to let you board
没有授权  -我们有地方要去
-It's not authorized. -We have somewhere to be,
我们得坐上直升机
so we need to be on that chopper
否则的话
and if we're not,
我会留出几十万美元
I'm gonna set aside several hundred thousand dollars
专门用来毁了你的生活
and I'm going to dedicate it to destroying your life
怎么样 听起来如何
Is that great? How does that sound?
我对此无法回应  -飞机走了
-I can't speak to that. --There she goes!
好吧 再见啦  -它要去哪 怎么回事
Okay, bye-bye. -Where's it going? What is this?
老爸走了
There goes Daddy
它回市中心了  -小鸟再见了
It's going back to the city. Buh-bye birdie
就这样吧  -天哪
There it is. -Oh, man.
跟老爸摆摆手 说再见
Wave bye to Daddy.
这他妈算什么 我们要迟到了
The fuck is this? Well, we're gonna be late now.
康纳要崩溃了
Connor's gonna shit.
这他妈是去月球的罪恶之旅
It's gonna be a guilt trip to the fucking moon.
该死的
God dammit.
在佛教里有时最折磨你的人
In Buddhism, sometimes your greatest tormentor
也可能是你最敏锐的老师
can also be, uh, your most perceptive teacher.
那…那真是智慧
That's... that's really wise.
佛爷
Um, hey, Buddha.
这身名牌衣服真帅
Nice Tom Fords.
这很有趣  -是康纳吗
-Okay, this is interesting. -Is it Con?
不是..
No, it's, um...
车在哪  -是桑蒂和斯图伊
Where's the car? -It's, uh, Sandi and Stew y
他们想…他们想面谈 电话或者面谈
they wanna... they wanna meet. Call or meet.
最好是面谈
They'd prefer the meet
他们问 我们能否在一到两个小时之内…
They're asking if we're gonna be back in the city..
回到市中心  -今晚吗
-in the next one to two. -I mean, tonight?
不是 关于董事会的事吧
No, it's about the board shit, right?
斯图伊说 桑蒂认为
Like Stew y says that Sandi thinks
从瑞典人那里可以榨取更多
there's more juice to squeeze from the Swede
他们又来这一套
so they're just flying that again.
是胡扯  -对
It's bullshit. -Yeah.
是胡扯 小西 我们继续
It's bullshit, Shiv. We've moved on.
我同意..  -车在哪儿
-I agree with this... --Hey! Where's the car?
他妈的嬉皮士  -他们去哪了
Fuckin'hippie. -Hey, where are they?
他们刚离开  -对 他们...我…
-They just left. --Yeah, they're... I..
他刚刚...  -叫辆车
He's just like... -Get a car!
在叫了 在叫车
I'm trying, I'm trying
董事会什么都不说 我不喜欢这样的沉默
Nothing from the board. I don't like this silence.
最后给他们打一次电话
Give'em one last buzz round
凯莉 让弗兰克和卡尔联系无党派人士
Kerry, get Frank and Karl on to the independents.
要三重保险
Let's triple lock this down.
预计宾州地区会有..
As severe thunderstorms are expected.
强雷暴
to hit Pennsylvania,
西弗吉尼亚弗吉尼亚..这东西到处都是
West Virginia, Virginia... -This shit's everywhere
还有今天的加利福尼亚州
And the Carolinas today
她在做什么  -来结束我们今天的预告
What is she doing? -To end our forecast...
你好  -我们结束得比较早 所以...
-Hey. -Hi. We finished early, so..
好的
Okay.
发生什么了  -什么
-What's going on? -Sorry?
只是 在准备董事会后的见面会
Uh, just some prep for post-board meet,
协议的签署
the signing of the deal
马特森好像很想和您会后拍个照
It seems Mats son would love an actual photo op
但 问题是
I guess the question is,
您想跟他拍照吗
is that something you would like?
还是 我们应该...  -你刚才在笑什么
-Or should we just... -What were you laughing at?
什么
What?
你刚才笑什么
What were you laughing at?
格丽在...我们刚才在聊
Uh, Gerri was... Um, we were chatting
她说了些有趣的事... 所以…
and she said... something amusing, so..
好吧 好吧 我们来看看有哪些选择
Okay, okay, let's look at the options.
我呢
Um, look, I, uh...
我不知道是否应该被公众看到
I don't know if I should be seen shaking.
我和马特森握手
uh, Mats son's hand
他在拆分泛美网科的事上 一直很不配合
I mean, he's been such a prick about the spin off.
好的 卡洛丽娜 你能放一下幻灯片吗
Okay, uh, Karolina, can you do the option deck?
你已经准备好了吧  -你可以来放吗
Well, you're ready to go in. -But can you do it?
你的电脑坏了吗
Is your laptop not working?
没有  -那你来呀
Nope. -Well, just give it a go.
刚才不是还能用吗 快点放
It appears to be working, give it a go.
好的
Okay.
看看..能不能行
See if it... see if it works.
好了
Here.
强烈的暴雨
Severe storm.
这是幻灯片..我们准备得很充分
So, here's the deck and it's... We got some great stuff here.
那我们开始吧  -我不想
So, um, should we get into it? -Look, I don't wanna be
看着像是精心准备过 懂吗
seen like some piece of fucking set dressing, okay?
唯一的问题是
I mean, the only thing is
每个人都在称赞 你交易的时机准确
everyone's saying the timing, the deal you've done,
你不想享受 被关注的时刻吗
don't you want your moment in the sun?
你已经开始为马特森工作了吗
Oh, you working for Matsson already?
我还在这呢 我还没走呢
I'm still here, you know? I haven't gone. Huh?
这么早就把维京人[入侵者]的帽子戴上了吗
You getting your Viking hat on early? Huh?
没有  -不行
-No. -Nah.
不行 全是胡扯
Nah, this is bullshit.
雨果 我们大概需要一个人
Hugo, I think we might need someone
去给一位独立董事拍马屁
to go and suck off an independent director.
我在担心董事们 你给我用心点
I'm concerned about the board. Put your fucking lipstick on.
好的
Okay.
上去会更糟吗
Is it worse to go up now?
我很不想去 可我们不得不去
I mean, I'd love to not go, but I think we kinda have
至少喝几杯马提尼
to drink at least a couple of
装装样子吧
Martini Passive Agresso s just to make up, right?
你们需要打车吗
Oh, you guys want a taxicab ride?
打车 来吧 来吧  -什么鬼
Taxicab? Come on, come on. Okay, what the fuck?
平价 我会给你们好价格
Flat rate. I'll give you good price.
好价格 好价格  -这是什么情况
Good price, good price. -Okay, what is this?
我们有点被逼迫的感觉  -来吧朋友
We're kinda pushed. -Yeah. Come on, man
你他爹的搞埋伏呢
is this a fucking ambush? Hi
不 我们只是想 私下五个人说这件事
No. We just wanted to do five in person.
对吧 桑蒂  -是的
Right, Sandi? -Yeah
我们在对面订了套房
we have a suite booked across the way
好吧 可现在真的不方便
Well, guys, it's not exactly convenient
我们准备在明天韦斯达的董事会上
We're prepared to vote no on the GoJo deal
对Gojo的收购投反对票
at the Way star board meeting tomorrow.
我们认为 可以从瑞典人那里榨取更多的钱
We think there's more money to be squeezed from the Swede,
而你们正因为情绪原因过于冲动
and we think you're rushing this for emotional reasons
好的 我不这么认为 好的 再见
Hmm. Well, I don't think so. Okay, see you
溢价在市场竞品中显得很弱 你知道的
The premiums look weak on market comparables, you know it
看看上周吧 小罗 那是另外一个交易
-Look at last week, Ro. -It's a different deal
不相关  -拜托 肯
it's not relevant. -Oh, come on, Ken
我们想要你爸多喊点价 但他不和我们谈了
We want your dad to ask for more, but he stopped engaging
他把我们搪塞给了卡尔 是他的作风
-He's palmed us off with Karl. -He does that
没了我们 交易也能完成
He can get the deal through without us
可如果我们能让你们加入
but if we can get you guys on our side,
我们可以逼迫他回到拳台上
we can force him back into the ring
再搏一轮
for one last round
好吧 那我猜董事会因为价格推迟会议
Okay, so I guess, like, board pushes back on price.
有什么大不了呢  -有什么大不了
What's the big deal? -What's the big deal?
好吧  -那我们必须权衡
Okay. -Well, we'd have to weigh that
这是否 会毁了一切
against the risk of blowing everything up
我们的状况是
I think our position might be that
刚刚从老爸那里挖了墙角
we're just done corn-holing our dad
可我们..我们觉得你老爸太激进了
But we... we just feel like your old man got hot for this.
可以让他冷静一下吗
Can't we cool him off?
听着 听着 我们每个人都拿得到钱
Listen, listen. There's money for all of us
只要我们好好讲 如果我们逼得紧就很危险
if we ask nicely. We push too hard, danger, danger
但钱就在那 你们知道 就在那
but, yeah, it's there. You know, it's there.
我爸很明确 他想投反对票
My dad is clear. He wants to vote no
没错,  -我们加上你们就够了
-Yes. -Us, plus you guys, that's it
他会被否决 没有通过董事会
He's outvoted. This doesn't get through the board
重新谈判
Send it back to the table
这不需要大动干戈  -当然 这..
-It doesn't need to go nuclear. -No. What..
不是什么大问题 我们就…
Okay, it's not a big deal, let's just...
我们会考虑的
We'll think about it. Yeah
董事会在明天
Okay, well, the board meeting's tomorrow
我们需要在一到两个小时内得到确认
So, we need to know in the next hour or two
好的 没问题  -好吗
Okay. Sure. -'Kay?
那 要么明天我们投票通过
So, it's either we vote yes tomorrow
大家都挣它上亿美元
and we all make billions of dollars,
或者 同意你们这个“冷静“的点子
or we sign up for your cool shit
然后老爸完全剥夺我们的继承权
and-then Dad dis inherits us entirely
好难抉择哦
That sounds like a toughie.
我们会考虑的 谢谢 再见
We'll think about it. Thanks. Bye
对 我们该走了  -肯
-Yeah. We gotta go. -Ken.
可以了  -肯
We're done. -Ken!
我会继续努力的  -我会给肯打电话的
-I'll keep working. -Yeah. And I'll call Ken
你好  -你好
-Oh, hey. -Hey.
你们才刚到啊
So, you're here now, huh?
是的 实在抱歉 怎么回事 你准备走了吗
Yeah. No, sorry. What, are you leaving or..
你没事吧
You okay?
没事没事 我没事 我只是
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm... I'm just
打算和别人再喝几杯
I'm just going for a little drink
已经结束了吗 办完啦
It's over? Is it done?
什么…婚礼彩排吗  -对
-The... the rehearsal? -Yeah.
还没有 不过
No, no, but I.
剩下的事情就交给他们好了
I think they can take it from here on
已经没我什么事了 所以…
Not vital from here, so...
通常来说 婚礼上
I mean, the bride is normally..
新娘总是第一波登场的
I guess, is generally considered one of the first team..
不是吗
in the old wedding, you know?
对 没错 我该走了
Yeah, right. Yeah, I should go.
好好想想 你也看到了我有点混乱
You know, and, have a think. I'm in a bit of a fuzz
活生生的现实的感觉 不是吗
Everything feels very vivid today, doesn't it?
你还好吧
You okay?
发生...什么了  -没事 挺好的
What... what's... -Yeah. Fine.
怎么了
What's going on?
就算再开心 也总会有累的时候吧
You can't be jumping for joy the whole time, right?
也是
No, I guess
话说..我该…我该走了
Yeah, look... I should, I should go.
好的  -好的 再见
-Okay. -Yeah, bye.
行 再见
Okay, bye.
童话般的婚礼
Fairy-tale wedding
但婚礼的新娘刚走了
There goes the bride.
我的钱不比老康少! 她看起来..
I have enough cash. -She is.
我不嫌弃她  -我们还要上去吗
-I'll take her. -I mean, do we even go up?
看起来已经结束了 看样子是的
It seems like it's over, so... -Well, I mean, yeah.
我们还是得上去呀  -你想怎么样
-I think we should. -What do you mean?
我们当然得上去了 你想怎么样
Yeah. Of course. --What do you mean? Yeah. No.
不是 我们得...我们还有很多事情得谈呢
No, we're gonna... We... we have a lot to discuss
什么 搅黄交易那事吗 得了吧
What? The fuck-y bullshit? No, come on.
罗曼 听着 再努力几周 我们就好起来了
Roman, look, a few weeks'pain could really set us up
我还觉得 咱们买皮尔斯
And I think we over-promised
买贵了  -不过是..
on Pierce and... -Just... It's a..
我只不过想
I just wanna...
不过是桑蒂在玩心眼  -我们得走了 快点
Sandi mind game. -We're gonna go. Come on.
去他们的 让他们见鬼去
Fuck'em. Fuck those guys
好吧
Sure.
终于到了  -在这呢
Finally. -Found him
终于
Finally...
可算到了
Here they are
你好 先生 抱一个  -不好意思 伙计
-Hello, sir. Hugs ie. -We're so sorry, man
感谢
Thank you.
老爹把我们害惨了 你好 老哥
Yeah, Dad screwed us. Hey, bro.
瞧瞧你们 反抗者联盟
Look at you. The Rebel Alliance.
防区里的情况怎么样
How is it out in those hills?
补给线健在吗 战略储备够不够
Supply lines okay? Got enough to eat?
大势已定了吗
This is how it is, huh?
准备大战一场 我和老爹一队
The battle royale. Me and Dad on one side.
你们仨一队
you guys on the other?
你..你还好吗 伙计 我们进来的时候
You... you okay, man? We bumped into Will a
碰见威拉了
on the way in.
没事 一切都挺好的
Yeah, I think it's all fine.
那就好
Yeah.
威拉正准备致辞 然后她突然来一句
Will a stood up to do her speech and she said.
不行 我做不到
" I can't do this.
之后跑到洗手间里 待了四十分钟
And she went to the bathroom for 40 minutes
和她那些所谓的朋友一起
with her so-called friends
我去 没事没事 小事 没有影响的
Jesus. Oh, no, no, no. No, that is not... You're fine
没问题的 你放心好了
That's totally fine. Don't worry about that
再扔给她几万块零花
Just toss her another ten grand
送她点礼物 雪地摩托或者牙齿美白券什么的
or a snowmobile and some teeth whitening vouchers.
怎么样了 西尔维娅
Any luck, Sylvia?
那是他岳母
Will a's mom.
没事的 老康
It's fine, Con.
那么... 真他妈邪门了
-Okay so...This is so fucking weird
要不回我那儿 聊一聊
Do we regroup at my place?
小西...人家这么悲催
Shiv. He's... Come on, he's looking a little rough
你不觉得吗  -是啊 看起来是的
don't you think? -Well, sure.
很抱歉 老爹摆了我们一道 搞得我们迟到了
I'm sorry that Dad fucked us, and I'm sorry that we're late
但我们得赶快下主意了 所以说…
but we do need to decide fast, so.
你说的 我们心里有底 不是吗  -当真如此吗
-Well, I think we know, right? -Do we, though?
没错  -他们提出的想法
-Yeah. -They made some
确实挺有吸引力的,  -桑蒂就是个贪得无厌的婊子
pretty compelling arguments. -Sand i's a greedy little bitch
她不过是在 操控她老爹这个空架子
She's got her hand up the ass of the carcass of her dad,
斯图伊不过是来凑热闹的罢了
and Stew y's just come along for the ride. It's a.
管他们呢 他们就是胡说三人组
Fuck it. It's a packet of horseshit
行 那如果是 我想好好谈谈呢
Okay. What if I want to talk it through?
我认为...根本没有谈论的必要 小西 你说呢
I just think... I think we rise above it, Shiv. Right?
我是说 没准
No... May be.
爸不像以前那样火力全开了
Dad is not on it like he used to be
又或者 他低估了预期
and maybe he's under played his hand
而且 董事会就是他一手提拔的
and the board are all a hand-fucking-picked
一群塑料招财猫 只会挥手同意他的决定
bunch of Japanese plastic cats just waving it through
好吧 还是没接通
Okay. Still incommunicado
希望她没事吧 那么 你们怎么说
I just really hope she's okay. So, what do you say?
要一起去唱卡拉OK吗
Little bit of karaoke?
这个宇宙里 除了卡拉OK以外 还有没有
Or would it be possible to do anything other than that
别的事情可以做呢 她都去嗨了 那我也可以去嗨
-in the entire universe? -She's partying, I can party
我们可以小喝两杯嘛 怎么样
I mean, we can go drink, right?
为未来的总统先生 办个小小的单身汉派对
Little bachelor party for POTUS-SCROT US
我们仨可能不是特别
Well, I mean, we three kind of.
当然了 大家都很忙  -我们还得
-Sure. Everybody's busy. -We've got a...
走吧 我们一起陪他喝一杯吧
Come on, let's give him a drink, sis
-太好了  -去陪他喝一杯
-Yeah. -Let's give him a drink.
太好了 不过…  -陪他喝一杯吧
Yeah, but not... but not... -Let's get him a drink
不要去那种烂大街的 得是真实的 有味道的酒吧
Your usual stupid places. Somewhere fun and real.
不要花里胡哨的 要实打实的酒吧
Away from the fancy dance. A real bar with chicks
里面有靓妹 有干重体力活的猛汉
And guys who work with their hands and grease,
手心里总冒汗 油油的
and sweat from their hands
头发丝里还残留着血
and have blood in their hair
我不喜欢这种男的
I don't like these guys
听起来像某种实验失败的产物
They sound like a medical experiment gone wrong.
我不知道 他刚刚说 这是个大问题
I don't know, he just said it's a big fucking problem
但 为什么非得在厨房里呢 我们还得把刀藏起来吗
Well, why the kitchen? Should we hide the knives?
不知道 他才说…
I don't know, he just said..
洛哥 怎么了
Loge. what's up?
全是披萨吗
Is all this pizza?
要这么多披萨干嘛
Why am I looking at all this pizza
简直要命
It's killing me.
这简直…全乱套了 汤姆
This is... It's out of control, Tom.
没错  -他们出去买新鲜的派了
Right. -They send out for fresh pies
但这里 还剩好几个 根本没动过的披萨
and there are two or three here already that are perfectly good
把它们放进微波炉里 热—热就可以了
All you have to do is put them in the fucking microwave.
好的  -好的 收到
-Right. -Right. Noted.
只是温馨提醒一下
I guess, just to say, it does tend to
这么做 可能不是特别健康
it loses a s... There's a sog factor..
格雷格 滚
Greg, fuck off.
好的
Okay.
其实 不是披萨的问题
it's not the pizza
我一直在考虑凯莉的事
I've been thinking about Kerry
这样啊 很激动人心啊 咱们好好计议一下
Okay. Okay. Yeah, very excited. I mean, let's get into it.
她简直就是为此而生的 很有潜力
She's a... she's a natural. She's got " It.
她已经可以出师了吗
Is she the finished article?
出师吗 不行
Well, finished article, no
您也不想她这么快出师吧  -当然
But you wouldn't expect her to be. -No.
对啦 她还需要点时间
No. She needs a little... Needs a little time.
也许 也许 还需要很长一段时间
May be, may be quite a bit of time.
有意思
Interesting
是的 她还很稚嫩
Yeah. She's, She's raw.
我想 也许我们可以考虑考虑
And I think, maybe we should think about
让她从一些台面下的小事做起
starting her way... under the radar.
您也知道 她还有很多要学的东西
And you know, she has a lot to learn.
很多
A lot.
而且我认为...太早把她放到聚光灯下
And I think... I think it can be damaging
或许会挫伤她的才能
to put talent out there too early
明智
Smart.
很明智的想法
Now, that's smart.
明白 好的 没问题
Yeah. Okay, sure. No problem
你的这些想法与我无关
I'm not involved. I'm nowhere near this
我对此可只字未提  -当然 明白
-I know nothing. -Sure. Understood
我大美国  -太"棒"了
America. -This is charming
好怀念这种感觉
I missed you
那么 你们都要点什么
Okay, what's everybody having?
你要什么
What do you want?
你觉得他们会做伏特加汤尼吗
Do you think they know how to make a vodka tonic?
酒吧桶装生啤酒 敢不敢
House red? Do I dare?
什么 算了算了  -好吧 就那个
What? No, no, no. -That. Get that
我就要密封的苏打水
Just a club soda with a sealed lid
从脏兮兮的喷嘴里出来的就算了
Nothing from that tainted nozzle
老康 你喝什么
Con, what do you want?
我来点 张三喝的 就可以
I'l I just have whatever a regular Joe would have.
比利时麦啤就好 最好不要福佳啤酒
Just, Belgian Weissbier. Not Hoegaarden, ideally
这个你看过吗  -什么
-Hey, have you seen this? -Hmm?
“华尔街见闻“ 报道的...
From " Heard on the Street "..
韦斯达最后的出价会是多少
About what the Way star price will come out at?
桑蒂转发了 所以我...
Sandi shared, so I..
你好 我要一杯伏特加汤尼
Hey, can I get, um, a vodka tonic
苦啤酒和苏打水
I'll have a bitters and soda.
老康 你还在吗
You still, uh, with us, Con?
当然 就是 威拉 我共享了她的定位
Oh, sure. Just Willa. I have her location shared
应该是出厂设置就有吧
I just think it's a factory setting
并没有
It's not.
不管怎么说 我安心了
Yeah, well anyway, I'm reassured
她肯定不在去古巴的路上
She's definitely not on her way to Cuba
至少她的手机不是  -好吧 她没动了
Well, her phone isn't. -Yeah, she's stopped moving
她应该是找到了想待的地方
I guess she found a spot she likes
当然  -在另一个男人的鸡鸡上
Sure. -On another man's dick
我是说
On a much bigger
在一个更大更棒更硬的鸡鸡上
nicer, harder, younger dick is all I'm saying.
我们能不能不...  -好的 对不起 我懂的
Can we not? Can we not, d... -Okay. Sorry. I know
兄弟 你懂的 因为我感觉
Dude. You know,'cause I'm feeling..
我...我有些焦虑 好吗  -好的 抱歉
I'm... I'm having certain anxieties, huh? -Okay, sorry
我是说 我...我是想好好玩儿的
I mean, I... I wanna have a good time.
好吧  -走 一起玩儿吧
Okay all right. -Let's have fun.
咱们一起监控她的移动轨迹
We can monitor her dot together
她...什么  -投屏到
She's... What? -Let's get it up
大屏幕上吧  -怎么待了怎么久..
on the big screen. -Why so long at the.
她定位在一个水族馆用品商店
Her dot is at a aquarium supply retailer.
这说不通啊 那儿是个毒窝吗
That doesn't make sense. Is that a drug thing?
我太爱他了  -不是的
I love him. -No
你确定吗
You sure?
我确定
I am sure.
是真的 就是个毒窝
It is. It's a drug thing
抱歉  -现在她又在干洗店了
Sorry. -Now, she's a t a dry cleaner's
她也许在送洗她的小内内
She's, uh, probably getting her panties cleaned
弄脏小内内了 真粗暴呢  -我接个电话
Mussed'em up a bit. That's really tough. -I'll be right back
你吃错药了吗  -喝的在这儿
What's wrong with you? -Drinks are right here.
我又没说是你的浆
I'm not saying it's your cum.
能不能别说了  -我相信你的浆非常…
-No, stop. -Your cum, I'm sure, is very.
闭嘴吧  -好洗 好的
Stop. Stop. -Washable. Okay.
卢卡斯 怎么了 兄弟
Yo, Lukas. What's up, brother?
怎么了
'Sup?
我他妈失眠了
I can't fucking sleep.
你睡眠好吗
You sleep good?
说实话 不咋地
Honestly, not really. No
受我尊敬的人 没一个睡眠好的
Well, I've never met anyone I respect who sleeps good
我懂你 兄弟 睁着一只眼睡觉警觉
Tell me about it. One eye open, bro. One eye open.
是啊 还有就是 我的团队说
Yeah. And secondly, my... my team says
虽然我不该跟你聊这个
I shouldn't be talking to you about this.
但是 管他呢
but,whatever
是这样...我一直听说
Well, I've been... I've been hearing that, uh
哄抬价格的积极分子们
the activists hustling on the price
想让你加入他们的
are trying to get you to join their little, uh
傻逼聚会 这是真的吗
scheisse party. Is that true?
这个嘛 我没法...
Well, I can't, uh.
我没法跟你说具体的 但是...
I can't give you a play-by-play, but..
我知道 你想搞砸你老爸的这个交易
Well, I.. I know that you tried to screw this deal with your dad
我也知道  他现在烦死你了
and I know your dad hates you now.
所以...
So...
你没得选了 是吧
You're out of options, huh?
我还听说 你最近到处跑
And I've also been hearing that you've been going around
准备给老太婆们送几箱子钱
offering old ladies suitcases full of money
如果你想很快收到一大箱子钱的话
Well, if you want to have a full suitcase anytime soon,
最好别给我压力 懂吗  -懂了 兄弟
you... you don't push me, okay? -Okay, dude
你别...他一定会卖的  -我懂你意思 兄弟
-You're... He's gonna sell. -I hear you, man.
但 如果他再给我压力 买的人就不是我了
But if he pushes me again, it won't be to me.
我不想咄咄逼人
This isn't aggressive.
有人跟我说过 有时候当我
Like, uh, I've been told that sometimes when...
当我直来直去的时候 会被解读为咄咄逼人
When I'm direct, it can code aggressive,
但并不是 只是...
but it's not, it's just.
听我说 我欣赏你 真的
Look, I like you, I like you. I do
我就是想把话说明白 你懂的 在核弹发射前
I thought clarity, you know, before any nukes get launched
好吗
Okay?
所以 要么你退一步 要么我退出
So, either back off, or I'm gonna walk
我懂你意思了 完全懂  -好的
-I got you, loud and clear. -Okay.
就这些 小肯 罗伊  -好的 好梦
I think that's it, K-Roy. -Yeah. Sweet dreams
东部地区已发布暴风警报
Storm warnings have been issued in parts of the east,
大暴雨预计将登陆宾夕法尼亚
as severe thunderstorms are expected to hit Pennsylvania
加利...卡罗来纳州 今日
and the Cali... Carolinas today
关于洛杉矶天气的预…
And our forecast to la..
格雷格 这是一次非常棘手的外交事件
This is an incredibly delicate piece of diplomacy, Greg
对吗 就像巴以冲突
Okay? It's like Israel-Palestine,
只不过 比巴以冲突更惨烈 更重要
except harder and much more important
她会很不高兴的
She's not gonna be happy
对
Right.
但我想到一个解决办法
But I think I see a way through
什么 你去告诉她
-What's that? -You tell her
是啊 真...有意思
Yeah, in... interesting
我是说 我...我不...我不喜欢这样
I mean, I... I don't... I don't like it
你以前不是挺壮志未酬的嘛
Well, you're a little frustrated?
我是
Yeah.
级别更高的任务这不就来了
You wanted next-level tasks, right?
但 我不想
Yeah, but not like
告诉我们老板的女朋友 她不能上电视
telling our boss'girlfriend she can't be on TV
说实话 我觉得..还是说得通
Honestly, I think... I think it tracks
你这样做 好吗
This is what you do, all right?
你去找她 然后你说 比如..
You go to her and you say... Like you say
想出头很难
" It's really hard
就算你是家族的表亲也不容易
even being the cousin of this family.
你也见识了孩子们的遭遇
and you've seen what's happened to the kids
你懂的 事情一团糟...
You know, things get muddled..."
然后 你告诉她 她很好 但没有太好
And... and then you tell her she's good, but not too good
然后你..你确保把洛根撇干净
and then you... you... You make sure Logan's out of it
把我撤干净 然后你跟她说
and I'm out of it and you tell her
焦点小组有些见解
that the focus group had thoughts
好的  -然后你问她
-Mm, okay. -And then you ask her, you know,
她真的想要这一切
does she even really want it
轻易地递到她手上吗
handed to her on a silver platter?
比如说 来自四面八方的民怨和指责
You know, with all the resentments and accusations?
然后 你可以让她以为 是她自己
And then you can make it seem like it's her idea
让节奏慢下来 好吗  -好的
-to cool things, right? -Okay
懂了吗 好  -好的
-Yeah? Good. -Yeah
但万一她说
But if she's like
操你爹 格雷格 老娘明天就要上电视
" Fuck you, Greg, and I wanna be on TV tomorrow.
泛美网科是我家...”  -这个嘛 那么 如果真发生了
ATN is my home..." -Well, then, if that happens,
就回到安全的位置
just back away to a position of safety
然后我会亮相 让她息怒 好吗
and I will march in and mop up the rage, okay?
好吧
All right.
该死
Oh, god dammit.
我玩儿的挺开心的
Well, I'm having fun.
咋样了 我错过什么了吗
Hey, what's up? What did I miss?
我们在吃东西呢
We're eating
是吗  -就这个
Yeah? -Right here.
比利? 雷? 赛勒斯牌的肯德基炸鸡粑粑
Billy Ray Cyrus's Kentucky Fried Shit Shack
这家看上去有些丰盛美食呢
Well, they seem to have some hearty fare
刚谁打的  -斯图伊
What was that shit? -Uh, Stew y
真棒 现在又他妈咋了
Oh, great. What the fuck now?
事实上 家人们 我能...
Well, actually, guys, can I... can I..
我能给你们看个东西吗
Can I show you something?
当然  -鸡翅耶
-Yeah. -Oh, wings!
真好奇他们从什么生物上咔嚓下这些翅膀的
I wonder from which particular creature they snip these wings
是...  -也许是哺乳动物吧
It's, um... -Perhaps a mammal
关于可比公司的
On the comparables.
这..这其实挺吸引人的
It's... it's actually pretty fucking intriguing
好吧 这会让你思考
Okay. Well, it makes you think
也许 爸不像以前那样火力全开了
May be Dad isn't on it like he used to be
他一直被马特森使唤来使唤去
You know, he's been pushed around by Mats son
还被凯莉逗得团团转
and fucking being pushed around by Kerry.
给他女朋友一档节目 这简直..
Giving shows to his girlfriend? That's just..
操 她在东河 她居然他妈的在..
Fuck, she's in the East River. She's in the fucking.
不对  -什么
No. -What?
她在桥上
She's on the bridge
她要去威廉姆斯堡
She's headed to, uh, Williamsburg
老康 我不想当混蛋
Not to be dicks, Con, but is it okay
但 我们能小范围讨论一会吗
if we do a little breakout chat,
就我们仨
just the three of us?
不会太久的  -什么
-We won't be long. -What?
最多就两分钟  -要不然
Like, two minutes max. -Hey, fuck it.
我们带上老康一起吧
Why don't we fold Con in?
这个嘛 他不在董事会 所以…
Well, he's not on the board, so.
是的 但他有股份 所以一旦交易
Yeah, but he has a share, so if the deal.
他也没法套现了
he loses his payout
什么玩意儿  -你没听错 小西想
Excuse me? -Oh, yeah. So, Shiv wants
把我们卷进 某场毒品交易
to get us mixed up in some sort of drug de a
会搅黄明天的大事
that will fuck the vote tomorrow
不对 小小地推迟 我们都希望能成交
Uh, no. A small delay, we all want the deal
好吧  -听着 我同意
Okay. -And, look, I think I agree.
现在他妈是闹哪一出  -对 就是
Oh, what the fuck now? -Yeah, just.
你认真的吗  -就是
Seriously? -It's just
看看那数字...
looking at the numbers...
怎么  -它..太诱人了
-Yeah. -It's... it's compelling
是啊  -诱人吗 拜托
-Yes. -It's compelling? Come on
所以 你要强迫爸臣服
So, you're gonna force Dad to grovel?
老天 重新谈判又要花多久
Oh, man. How long will a renegotiation take?
这只是一种招数
It's a play.
钱是实打实的 而这就是我们要的
More money is more money and that's all there is to it.
不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
罗曼...
Uh, Roman...
爸给你发短信是要干什么 小罗
The fuck is Dad messaging you for, Rome?
我不知道 你问他吧
Uh, I don't know. Ask him
这问题太蠢了
Stupid question.
你不看消息吗
You're not gonna read it?
我会看的...我会的
Yea h, I'll read the... I will, yeah
我当然会看 就是问个好
I'll read it, sure, Um, uh, just a check-in.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
问好吗  -是啊 没错
A check-in? -Yeah. Yeah.
是吧 你是对的 爸可太会这么做了
Oh, yeah, you're right. Classic Dad.
他经常来问个好
He always just checks in
看看你过得如何
Just wants to see how you're doing
我就是在他生日的时候
Okay, I sent him a text on
发信息跟他说“生日快乐
his birthday just saying, " Happy birthday.
"抱歉我们错过了”  -什么
Uh, " Sorry we missed it." -I'm sorry.
等一下 是你先发短信给他的
wait a minute. You texted him initially?
在他生日那天 是的
On his birthday. Yeah
我们说好了 他道歉之前不联络的
We said no contact until he apologizes
所以 那就是永远不联络了吗
Okay, well, so then, never?
你知道吗  -什么
You know what? -What?
我想看下你的手机
I think I would like to see your phone.
真的吗  -是的
-Oh, really? -Yeah.
给我看看你的手机 世界上最大的即时通讯软件群组
Show me your phone. World's biggest What s App group
都在分享你骚逼的照片
of people sharing pictures of your snatch
才不要 去你妈的 不给你看  -小罗 两位 小罗
No, thanks. Fuck you. No. -Rome? Guys? Rome
干嘛
What?
我们必须相互信任
We have to trust each other here
那就他妈的看吧 我无所谓
So then fucking look. I don't give a shit.
很好  -反正都是鸡巴照
Great. -It's dick pics anyway.
他现在对它可是爱不释手  -好啊
He's got a real taste for'em now. -Great.
就在这了 看吧 谁他妈在乎
It's this right here. Read. Who gives a shit?
还不止一条短信
Well, this is more than one text
两条三条就..  -是啊
-It's two, three. It's... -Yeah.
超过一条了 真是对不起
Yeah, it's more than one. Sorry.
还挺温馨的  -温馨 怎么 我说了什么
It's a bit warm. -It's warm? Why? What did I say?
"保重"  -"保重
-" Take care." -" Take care "?
不然我要怎么说“生日快乐
What am I supposed to say? " Happy birthday
祝你从楼梯上摔下去 傻逼
Hope you fall down a flight of stairs, shithead.'
怎么说呢 你这种背叛的行为
You know what? I feel a little bit weird
让我感觉怪怪的
about this betrayal
背叛  -是的
The betrayal? -Yeah
对 你说的背叛是指
Yes, the... the betrayal of,
生日快乐 爸爸 保重 罗曼"这样吗
" Happy Birthday, Dad. Take care. Roman.
你知道吗  -嗯
You know what? -Yeah
这能叫背叛 -我也有同感
Betrayal? -I do, too.
真他妈离谱 他妈的家庭忏悔之旅
Okay, great. Fucking family guilt trip
那去欧洲度假好了 走吧
European vacation. Let's do it
这很难 我知道大家都不好受
It's hard. It's been hard on everybody
你知道 他就离婚的事 给了汤姆不少建议吧
You know that he advised To m on the divorce?
传授他的专属技能
Gave him a Dad trick
让他去找了 曼哈顿所有的离婚律师
Went and spoke to every pit bull in Manhattan, tied'em up
我重走了老妈的路
I got Mom med.
你要找的话
I mean, there's probably one more
美国某地应该
horrible motherfucker lawyer
还有其他的糟糕无良律师
somewhere in the United States if you wanna look
但 那确实很糟心
but, um, yeah, that sucks, I'm sorry.
家人们 我觉得我们得团结一致
Guys, I feel like we need to stick together
我们应该还以颜色 你应该加入我们
And we should push back, and you should come with us
我们要对爸施加压力
and we should put the squeeze on
好 但我们要买皮尔斯对吧
Okay, but, we want to do Pierce, right?
我们要摆脱这一切  -没错
We want to out, right? -Yes.
对 就是这样  -好
Yeah. Yeah, exactly. -Okay
就是为了多赚点钱
Just with just a bit more money
好 但我不觉得马特森会加价
Yes, but I don't think Mats son will go up in price
他不会的 因为我跟他聊过这事
He won't. I know this because I have spoken to him
如果...如果他是这么说的
Oh, well, if that's... If that's what he said
那肯定就是真的了  -说真的
then it must be true. Yeah. -Okay, seriously
我觉得他会放弃  -是吗
I think he might walk. -Oh, might he?
是的  -你觉得
-Yes. -Yeah, do you think
有没有一种可能 就是
he could may be, like, is it a possibility
他说的话是...  -好吧
he could say a... A not... -Okay
说的不是真的 是假话呢
Like a thing that isn't, a lie?
那他为什么要这么说
I mean, why would he say that?
这是谈判的基本操作 小罗
Well, it's Negotiating 101, Rome.
他们在管理培训课上没有教你吗
Did they not teach you that in management training?
好吧 但他...听起来很真诚
All right, but he... It sounded like he meant it.
得了吧 那就是第二项基本操作
Oh, yeah. That's Negotiating 102
好吧  -这非常基础
-Okay. -It's pretty basic
我知道 冲突不是好事
Look, I know the conflict isn't nice,
但我们给皮尔斯承诺的价格太高了...  -等等 什么
but we over committed on Pierce... -Wait, what?
这样我们的钱就..  -我才不在乎
-And this gives the cash... -I don't give a shit
会产生冲突  -那就好好干
about conflict. -To make it right.
我他妈就是冲突本身
Like, I will conflict fucking conflict.
是的 好吧  -不 我不是
-Yes, you do. Oh, okay, fine. -No, I don't
那 这 事关你对爸的感情了
Well, it is about Dad feelings for you then
对爸的感情  -是啊
Dad feelings? -Yeah
如果现场 他妈的还有人在乎他的感受
If anyone here has fucking Dad feelings,
那他妈可就是 举着叉子怼撒旦啊
it's holy shit, poking Satan with the fork
我真的是为了我们仨
I'm genuine about us three.
你们别再 像列侬和麦卡特尼一样 联合起来对付我
And stop ganging up on me like you're Lennon and Mc Cartney
把我当他妈的乔治 我是约翰 混球们
and I'm fucking George. I'm John, motherfuckers.
林戈 洋子
Ringo, Yoko.
他还是康纳 但
He's still Connor, but
他靠拍卖赢得跟我们同桌饮酒的机会
he won having drinks with us at an auction
说真的
Honestly, though
我觉得...和桑蒂以及斯图伊合作
I think... going with Sandi and Stew y
对我们来说是最好的...
is... is the best thing for us to do..
对 作为一个团队
Yeah. As a team.
就是...就是一招
It's just a... it's just a move
稍微拖延几个星期
It's a... it's a delay, a couple weeks
他会得偿所愿的 爸全盛时期也这么做
He'll get it. It's what Dad would do in his prime.
没错
Exactly.
如果只是一招 那行吧
I guess if it's just a play, then yeah
他妈的 我加入
Fuck, yea h, I'm in.
真他妈的该死
God fucking dammit
真他妈的该死  -抱歉 抱歉
God fucking dammit. -Sorry. Sorry
你们毁了一切 全他妈被你们毁了
You ruined it all, you fucking ruined it all
老康 老康  -抱歉
Con, Con, Con. -Sorry.
你们毁了一切
You fucked it up
你想怎么做  -我想怎么做
-What do you wanna do? -What do I want to do?
我想明天结婚
I wanted to get married tomorrow
那..  -我想今晚
-Well... -I wanted to spend tonight
和家人一起过 明天和爸一起
with my family and tomorrow with my dad
我他妈的想把自己的钱拿出来
and I wanted to get my fucking money out
我们还能怎么做
What else can we do?
我想去卡拉OK 他妈的唱一首歌
I would like to sing one fucking song at karaoke
因为我在电影里看过
because I've seen it in the movies,
但没人愿意去
and nobody ever wants to go.
凯莉 抱...抱歉
Hey, hey, Kerry, um, s... sorry.
请问 我能稍微耽误[同义"揩油"] 您五分钟吗
can I possibly please, uh, grab you just for five minutes?
很快的 就现在  -行 有何不可
Quickly, please, right now? -Yeah, why not?
毕竟曼哈顿的其他女人你都揩过了
You've already grabbed every other woman in Manhattan.
谢谢 我们...进来这边谈
Thank you. Let's... let's just head in here.
我只是想稍微耽误你几分钟
I just wanted to grab you for a quick moment
我...我希望这样没有太过逾越
Um, uh, I... I hope I'm not getting above my station here.
但我想跟你聊下 试镜带的事
Um, but I wanted to talk to you about the whole tape thing
我不太确定该跟你聊这件事
Oh, I... I'm not sure I wanna talk to you about that
对 我理解 那就是作为朋友…
Oh, yeah. No, fair enough. Then, just as a friend I.
我想私下里给你提个醒
I wanted to give you a heads up on the down-low
主要是针对公司内的流言蜚语
on what the murmurs are, and say, you know
比如 作为家庭成员
how careful I have had to be
我要如何谨慎地处理我的特殊地位
about my particular position as a family member
以及外人对裙带关系
and say how people chatter so unpleasantly
喋碟不休 让人很不愉快的指责
about accusations of legs-up
还有不公平的...   -到底想说什么 格雷格
and unfair... -What is this, Greg?
就是…
Just…
你...你是否…
Are... are you...
有点操之过急了
rushing things a bit?
而这...在长期看来
And could... Could that, long term
会影响你的地位..  -所以 汤姆觉得
-actually harm your position... -So, okay, Tom doesn't think
我还没准备好 所以他派你...  -不不不
-I'm ready and he's sent you... -No, no, no.
不不不 不是这样
No, no, no, not at all.
他觉得你很棒
Uh, he thinks you're great
但是 焦点小组内部对你尚有疑虑
I mean, there's some little doubts from a focus group
他们...  -他们组织了焦点小组吗
and they're... -They focus-grouped me?
是的 但...但核心是.. 听我说
Yes. But... but the big picture is, what I'm saying.
肯德尔和小西
You know, like, how Kendall and Shiv
争权夺利  -好吧 抱歉
-have an entitlement problem? -Okay, I'm sorry
焦点小组是怎么说的
What did they say, the focus group?
总体评价不错
Uh, well, headlines, great..
只是 可能...力不胜任
just maybe not fully there.
也有一些负面评价
And a few criticisms,
但是...但是...  -比如呢
but... but... -Such as?
小问题而已 不必在意 形象不错
Uh, minor shit, like, nothing. I mean, may... Great package
也许有点手臂...手臂不对
Uh, may be a little, you know, arm... the arms aren't right
有点不上镜
you know, or they're a little un-TV
手臂不对 是吗
The arms aren't right?
是的 但...但不是什么大问题
No... Yeah, but... but not a biggie
日后可以改善
No, it's fixable with a few years
但是抱歉 这是在镜头前
But, uh, no sorry, on TV, this is on TV
在所难免 可能拍得不好 相机问题
and it can happen th... that they shoot weird, the cameras..
焦点小组里有什么人 格雷格
So, who was in this focus group, Greg?
只有你吗
Just you?
不是  -有汤姆吗
-No. -Is it Tom?
没有  -有洛根吗
-No. -Logan?
没有
No.
是…是一群
It... it's a bunch
老的老 傻的傻 的人
of grandpas and little twerp s and such.
我能看名单吗  -不行
Can I see it? -No.
为什么  -因为这是非公开的
Because? -Because it's private
并不是  -你不能看
-Well, it's not. -You can't.
如果是洛根想看呢  -这...我很抱歉
What if Logan wants to see it? -It's... I'm sorry
这是机密  -对首席执行官也保密吗
it's confidential. -From the CEO?
是的  -好 如果这个焦点小组是假的
-Yes. -Okay. If this focus group isn't real
我一定会把你大卸八块
I'm gonna take you apart like a human string cheese.
明白
Understood
任务完成 任务完成
I did the job. I did the job
我收到了康纳的信息
Heard from Connor.
他说什么
Okay?
孩子们 桑蒂和斯图伊 他们的票数够了
The kids, Sandi and Stewy, they have the numbers
我们得从长计议了
to force us back to the table
你准备怎么办要我打给他们吗
W... what? What do you do? You want me to call?
要我帮你痛骂他们一顿吗
You want me to ream'em out for you?
不要 谨慎一点
No. Delicate.
他们有两把刷子
They have some juice here.
他们还真有两把刷子
They have some fucking juice.
你应该和威拉共享定位
You should share your fucking dot with Willa
她就能知道你在外面撒野了
Then, she'll see that you're out having fun
我喜欢唱K
I love karaoke,
太棒了 你的婚礼吹了
it's great. Boo, boo! Your wedding is doomed
我只是说 可能
I said may be
好 谢谢
Okay. -Thank you.
所以 现在是什么情况
So, what happens now?
某人要在耻辱宫殿里
Uh, well, someone has to humiliate themselves
羞愧得抬不起头来了
in the shame palace.
你觉得这里有老鹰乐队的"亡命之徒"吗
Think they have " Desperado " By The Eagles?
应该有吧 今晚注定难熬啊
I would imagine they do. Longest night of my life
该死
Oh, shit.
怎么了 -她的定位消失了
-What? --She's gone dark
为什么她的定位消失了 就这样了吗…
Why has she gone dark? I mean, is this it?
她不会是跟小伙子出去鬼混
Is she going off with some buck
然后 他们你懂的..  -别胡思乱想了
and they're gonna, you know? -Hey, take it easy
可能..可能她手机没电了
May be... may be her phone just died.
是的 你有没有想过
Yeah. Have you ever considered
她可能并不适合你
that she might not be right for you?
这也许是好事 对吧
This could be good. Yeah?
康纳  -你会遇到更好的人
Connor? -You'll meet someone else
你找不到比威拉更好的了
You're not doing better than Will a
我同意 别让威拉走
I would agree. Do not let Will a go
罗慕路斯
Romulus
所以 爸在路上了
So, Dad's on his way.
什么  -等他到了
What? -He wants us to meet him
他想让我们下楼
down at the car
去车里见他  -什么鬼
when he gets here. -What the fuck?
他怎么知道我们在这里
How does he know we're here?
你怎么知道他来了  -我跟他说
-How do you know he's coming? -Well, I told him
今晚有不少人在左右横跳
that it's the night of a thousand wobbles over here
他需要跟你们谈谈  -你疯了吧 老康
and he needs to talk to you. -Oh, for fuck's sake, Con
我的生活不像有些人那样神神秘秘
My life isn't filled with secrets like some people.
我心直口快
I share things.
并且我希望父亲能参加我的婚礼
And I want my father to be at my wedding
你是说 你想要钱  -不是 西沃恩
You mean you want the money? -Well, no, Siobhan,
那不是我的首要考量
that was not my primary consideration.
我们该怎么办 我们...我们要走吗
I mean, what do we do? Do we... do we leave? I mean..
他会进来吗 他不会 对吧
Will he come in? He's not coming in, right?
你知道吗 心静如水 我的朋友
You know what? Just be water, my friend.
心静如..."谢谢你了 兄弟
" Just be wat "... Wow, thanks, man
如果我杀了个信佛的会怎么样
What happens if I kill a Buddhist?
我会转世成为信佛的吗
Do I get reincarnated as a fucking Buddhist?
希望他不会来
I hope not.
现在是凌晨四点 十二月底
It's four in the morning. The end of December
我写信给你 想知道你是否安好
I'm writing you now Just to see if you're better
纽约很冷 但是我喜欢我住的地方
New York is cold. But I like where I'm living
整夜 克林顿街
There's music On Clinton Street
余音绕绕
All through the evening
真是关塔那摩监狱[虐囚丑闻频出]级灾难
This is Guantanamo-level shit
我听说 你在建造…  -你在唱什么 老康
-I hear that you're building -What is this, Con?
你的小房子..
Your little house...
我想听"亡命之徒" 可以吗
I think I'd like to hear " Desperado." Please?
在沙漠深处
Deep in the desert
你活得毫无意义
You're living for nothing.
好吧 我不知道爸为什么打给我
Uh, okay. I don't know why Dad's calling me
是吗 他应该打给我的
Well, really he should be calling me.
我们说什么来着 不要接
What did we say? Don't answer it.
我没接
I'm not.
按掉
Hang up.
我可以...干嘛 我本来想让它响完的
I could just, uh... Hey! I was gonna let it ring out
该死 当然可以 我没想到这一点
Oh, shit! Of course. I didn't think of that.
用你的一缕头发
Mm, with a lock of your hair
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
都在啊
Hey.
该死
Oh, shit.
能换个地方吗 这些灯
Can we, uh, go somewhere else? These lights are.
我会癫痫发作的
I could have a seizure
我们哪也不去  -好 很好
We're not going anywhere. -Fine. Very well
好吧
Okay.
我们不需要你在场 凯莉 你可以...
Uh, we won't be needing you, Kerry. You can...
是啊  -谢谢
Oh, yeah. -Thank you
毕竟是家务事 所以...
This here is a... A family fuck-fuck, so.
无视我吧
Ignore me.
好吧 把事情说清楚
Okay, let's get this figured out
你们就可以继续玩了
and then I can let you get back to your fun
可能得让你白跑一趟了
Well, it might've been a wasted trip
想给我们唱一首“纽约纽约"然后打道回府吗
Wanna give us a quick blast of " New York, New York " And fuck off?
我有话要说
Well, I... I wanted to say something
是吗 想说服我们全票赞成出售吗
Yeah? Reasons we should vote through the sale?
意料之中
It's... No surprises there
除非你用"伊帕内玛女孩"的调子唱出来
Unless you do it to the tune of " The Girl From Ipanema.'
不是那件事... 除了那件事
Well, um, it's not that. I mean, um, uh, aside from this
我想 我...
um, I guess I..
I guess I just...
其实 我有点想让你们 来参加我的派对的
I... I wanted you there a bit at my party
天啊
Holy shit
爸刚才说出了他的感受吗
Did Dad just say a feeling?
你们知道的 我只是…
Well, you know, I just..
我想这样对大家都好
I thought maybe it would be nice.
该死 现在... 气氛烘托到这儿了
Oh, fuck. Now... now, it's all coming out.
天啊 戏剧大师飙演技了
Oh, my God, Mr. Melodrama over here
好一出狗血肥皂剧
It's like a fucking telenovela
拜托 兄弟们 他在示好
Come on, guys, he's trying something
你们知道的 我早就
Look, you knew I wanted Pierce
想收购皮尔斯了
from way back.
当我输了的时候
And when I lost out.
感觉很不好
that was not a good feeling
好吧 你少来了
Yeah, no shit.
我们几乎是从奥尔巴尼走回来的
We practically had to walk back from Albany
我们能不能...抱歉...我们能废话少说吗
Can we just... I'm sorry. Can we cut the shit?
你的来意太明显了
It's obvious why you're here
你们的父亲想解决一些私事
Your father wanted to address the personal stuff
不仅仅是想直接谈公事
and not just launch into the business
你看 这不是私事 爸
Well, see, this isn't personal, Dad
这是公事 跟钱有关
Uh, this is a business decision. This is about the money.
听着 你问钱的事是明智的 真的
Look, you're smart to ask about the money, you are.
但 马特森不会如你所愿
But Mats son won't go there
你们没有经历过 但我是过来人
You haven't been around this, but I've got done a good deal,
你们会得到足够的钱 去做你们想做的事
and you'll get enough to do whatever you want
我经营泛美网科 你们经营皮尔斯
I do ATN, you do Pierce.
这对我们来说 都是一个新的开始
It'll be a fresh start for all of us
从现在开始 情况会越来越好
It'll make things better, and it starts there.
你们只需要投赞成票 促成这桩交易
All you have to do is vote yes and support the deal
你们明白 这意味着什么吗
Do you know what he's offering?
这样 你们就可以把生意场 和家事分开
You can separate the personal and the business, you can...
重新恢复你们作为家人的关系
Hmm. Reset your dynamic as a family
那可太棒了
Oh, super.
这样我们就能回到以前那样
We gonna be just how we, like, we used to be
在一起过暑假
and... and... and go on summer va cay together
像音乐剧里一样 开着车 唱着歌 去旅行吗
and drive down Route One in an RV singing show tunes?
可能比那个要复杂一点
It may be more complicated than that.
我知道 或许
Yeah, I mean, I guess
你的蜜月还没度完
you're still in the honeymoon period
还要上电视播节目
so... getting your own show on TV
难道你现在上不成电视了吗 真的吗
Oh, are you not gonna be on TV now? No?
不好意思 难道不是…
I'm sorry, is thATNot..
他不会出尔反尔了吧
Has he fucked you on that?
反悔是迟早的事
That'll happen, the fucking
不过 恭喜你也尝到这种背叛的滋味了
But congrats on losing your betrayal cherry
够了
Enough.
我以为 你们会想得到我的道歉
I thought you'd be interested in an apology
但是我受够了  -等等 不好意思
but that... that's enough. -Wait, I'm sorry
你说什么 什么道歉 我们没听见啊
An apology? We... we missed that.
听着 我不是那种会道歉的人
Look, I don't do apologies.
但 要是道歉 对你们 真那么重要的话…
but if it means so much to you..
那么 对不起
then sorry
现在你说什么
There's nothing you could say to me now
我都不会信了
that I would ever believe.
重谈这桩交易能让我们多赚一亿 爸
This deal push could be worth 100 mil to us, Dad
有那么多钱 我们能买到多少道歉
How many sorry s do we get for that?
好吧 说白了...
Okay, to be clear...
你到底是为了什么感到抱歉呢 爸
What are you actually sorry for, Dad?
这个嘛 首先
Well, I'm sorry
直升机的事 我很抱歉
for the helicopter for a start
各位 他为今天不让我们上直升机的事道歉呢
You guys, he's sorry about the helicopter from today
我猜这是一桩大事了
Well, that's the big one, I guess.
真的要说这些吗 爸  -好吧
Are we actually doing this, Dad? -Okay
因为要我说 你心知肚明
Cause I think, you know..
我们走到今天这步 还要追潮至…
Seriously, what fucked all this was when..
在意大利跟妈一起的时候  -好吧
-with Mom and Italy... -Yeah, okay
我也想过这个
I've had certain thoughts about that
听着 我的出发点是好的
Look, with the best of intentions,
我掌握着控股公司的结构
I, uh, I got the structure of the holding company
还有家族信托的所有权结构
the ownership structure of the, um, family trust
我可能没有说清楚
There is a lack of clarity and may be
让你们产生了这样的一种印象
maybe you got certain impressions..
真“棒” 要不你现在癫痫发作吧
Amazing. You sure you're not having that seizure?
他已经尽力了 不是吗 你们自己说的
I mean, he is trying, right? And what you said
你们只是想要一个道歉
you were interested in was an apology
好吧 还有别的吗
Okay, then. Anything else?
说啊 爸 你为什么感到抱歉
Come on, Dad. What are you sorry for?
抱歉 忽视了康纳的
Sorry for fucking ignoring Connor
整个人生  -你说太重了
his whole life? -Bit strong
在小罗还是孩子的时候打他
Hitting Rome when he was a kid?
这没啥 所有人都打我
Oh, no. I mean, everyone hit me.
我就是很招人烦
I'm fucking annoying
抱歉把康纳的妈妈关起来
For having Connor's mother locked up?
能不能不要搞金牌调解员这一套
Can we not do a whole show trial here?
那 给汤姆提供离婚建议这条呢
What about advising Tom on my divorce?
怎么样 说这个还有点用
Yeah? I mean, that one... That took effort
这可真是太过分了
That was above and beyond
汤姆向我咨询建议
Tom asked me for advice
我给他推荐了几个人
I recommended someone he could speak to
你当时又不在
You weren't around
如果你在  我会给你
If you'd been around, I would've offered you
同样的建议
the same advice.
你又不见我 我要怎么帮你
But I can't help you if you won't see me.
听着 简而言之 如果我们要价提高
Look, the bottom line is if we ask for more money.
马特森就跑了 我是知道的  -不 你不知道
Mats son walks. I know that. -No! You don't know that!
你不懂这个人
You don't know him!
你他妈不是什么都知道
You don't fucking know everything
你这么说 不代表这就是真的
Just'cause you say it doesn't make it true.
每个人都赞同你 相信你
Everyone just fucking agrees with you and believes you
你说的就成真了 然后你就到处炫耀
so it becomes true and then you can turn around
看到了吧 我就说我是对的
and say like, " Oh, you see? See? I was right."
但事情不是这样的 你就是个PUA大师
But that is not how it is. You're a human fucking gaslight!
好吧
Fine.
听着 我只是想咱们聚在一起
Look, I... I just want to get us all together.
你们这些孩子不懂 这是一笔好买卖
What you kids don't realize, this is a good deal
全世界都赞同 这笔交易是有价值的
The world likes it. It makes sense.
但到手的鸭子也是会飞走的
But deals have a habit of disappearing
马特森这种人 说变就变 说生气就生气
because pricks like Mats son get pissed off or snap. This..
这都是真实会发生的
This is fucking real
好吧 我可以代表大家说一句话吗
Okay, well, I think I can speak for everyone, can I?
找他再要点钱
When I say, " Go ask him for more money.
为什么呢  -商业意识
But why? -Just good business sense.
要挣我们自己的钱
Gotta make our own pile
对不对 爸  -少来了
-Right, Dad? -Oh, come on!
是啊  我的直觉就是这么跟我说的
Yeah, I mean, it's what my gut is telling me
我必须听从我的内心 我只有靠这个才能继续下去
and so I gotta listen to my gut. It's... it's all I got to go on.
天哪
Jesus.
你们这群蠢货 根本不是干正事的人
You're such fucking dopes. You're not serious figures.
我爱你们
I love you...
但你们真的..
but you are not...
烂泥扶不上墙
serious people
这傻逼 他们应该出来看看这里
Look at this prick. They should get out here.
还有傻女人 在给他热罐头当晚饭
Some cunt doing the tin cans for his supper
里面全是添加剂 你敢尝吗
take a sip of that medicine.
这座城市… 老鼠有臭鼬那么肥
This city... The rats are as fat as skunks
它们见到人甚至都不跑了
They hardly care to run any more.
我不明白 我他妈真不明白
I don't know. I don't fucking know.
会议取消
The meeting's off
我要去会会马特森 只要 你 我
I need to see Mats son. It'll be you, me
汤姆 卡尔 弗兰克参加
Tom, Karl, Frank.
不带格丽  -好的
But no Gerri.  -Fine.
跟老爸对着干 感觉怎么样
So, how was it for you? Fucking Dad
真爽 就是结束得太快了
Amazing, just over too soon.
我还能再继续下去呢
I could've kept going
小罗 我们开玩笑呢 都是玩笑
Rome, we're kidding, man. Kidding
我知道 没关系 真有意思
No, I know. It's fine. It's cool
我要回家了
Okay. I'm going home.
我相信她肯定会联系你的 老康
Well, I'm sure she'll be in touch, Con.
你知道吗 其实没关系的
You know what? It's fine.
真的吗  -真的
-Really? -Yeah.
身处在一个 不爱你的家庭里 的好处
The good thing about having a family
就是 你能学会 没有爱要怎么生存下去
that doesn't love you is you learn to live without it
你说什么啊 老康
What? Con...
你们都追着老爸 跟他说
You're all chasing after Dad, saying.
爱我吧 求你爱我 我需要爱
" Love me, please love me. I need love.
“我需要你的关注”  -这跟刚刚发生的一切
-I need attention." -I think that's the opposite
恰恰相反吧  -你们都是对爱如肌似渴的海绵
of what just happened. -You're needy love sponges
而我 是长在岩石上
And I'm a plant that grows on rocks
靠 死在我身上的昆虫 活下去的草
and lives off insects that die inside of me
天哪 老康
Jesus Christ, Con
威拉如果不回来也没关系
If Will a doesn't come back, that's fine.
因为 我不需要爱 这是我的超能力
Because I don't need love. It's like a superpower.
如果她回来了 但是不爱我
And if she comes back and doesn't love me.
也无所谓 因为我不需要
that's okay, too,'cause I don't need it
谢谢你们的派对
Thanks for the party
不用谢
Yeah, you're welcome.
马克·雷文海德
Mark Raven head
和杰瑞德·门肯 将在明晚亮相
and Jery d Mencken is coming up tomorrow night
敬请期待
It really is a must watch
我来了 爸
Hey, Dad.
瞧瞧这是谁啊 明尼苏达小村夫
Hey! Lookie, lookie here. Twin Cities Tessie.
我就说 怎么闻到了奶味
I thought I smelled dairy
刚才的事儿 还挺尴尬的
So, um, that just felt a bit weird
一下子发生那么多事
and there was a lot going on, so..
我们都知道 他们就那个样子
Oh, we know what they're like
我推迟了董事会 我想让你明天跟我一起
I've pushed the board meeting, I want you to come with me
去见见马特森 你能帮上我的忙
and see Mats son tomorrow. I could use your help
是吗
Oh, yeah?
但是 明天老康的婚礼怎么办
Uh, I mean, it's the wedding. Con's wedding
可这有点… 好吧 再说吧
Uh, but that feels... Yeah, let's see.
汤姆
Tom?
好 你们先聊  -谢谢
Yea h. I'll give you a moment. -Thank you
没事
Okay, yeah, sure
给  -好
Here. -Okay.
长刀之夜"历史事件正在酝酿之中
There's a Night of the Long Knives coming.
希德没戏唱了 我要重塑泛美网科
C yd's to as t. I'm reinventing ATN
我需要一个玩火的人
I need a fire-breather
一个天不怕地不怕 不择手段的冒险家
A ruthless fuck who'll do whatever it takes.
我该走了  -你跟皮尔斯八字不合
-May be I should go. -You're not Pierce.
聪明人知道自己的身份
Smart people know what they are
你真的需要我帮你管泛美网科吗
I mean, you really want me at A TN?
不只这个 罗慕路斯 不只
More, Romulus. More.
我需要你
I need you.